# **LAUTARO**

## **CABRERA**

Project manager / Account executive



Argentinian, 30 years old. I am a professional with a creative and practical mind. Constantly expanding knowledge on my fields of interests. A focused person, skilled on problem solving, decision-making, time management, negotiation and leadership. I am able to handle high volume of workload maintaining a life-work balance.

Clear communication is key, and team work is a must. I want to help others reach their maximum potential.

I am looking for new challenges for the next 3-5 years where I can boost my career which can help me settle overseas.



lautacabrera@gmail.com



+33 628746906



14 Bis Rue du Languedoc, Servies-En-Val, France.



**Lautaro Fabian Cabrera** 

### Lenguages

**Spanish** 

**English** 

**French** 

#### **Skills**

- Advanced Excel skills (pivot table, macros, formulas)
- Microsoft tools (Teams, One note, Word, PowerPoint, Power BI)
- Clouding (Drive, SharePoint designer)
- Finance, Tax & Accounting understanding.
- Trends, forecast and Financial calculations
- Data Analytics
- Strategist, visionary, resilience.

#### Other interests



MUSIC







**FOOTBALL** 



## **Education**



CNAM – projet de management.

Paris, France. (Sep 2020 – Present)



EDENZ - English language / Business course.

Auckland, New Zealand (Feb 2017 – Aug 2017)



Asoc. Arg. de publicidad – Advertisement. Buenos Aires, Arg. (2013 – 2015)



Univ. de Buenos Aires - Business management. Buenos Aires, Arg. (2009 – 2013)

- JavaScript algorithims and data structure certification. 300h online course (Present).
- SENIOR program, sponsored by EY. Atlanta, United States (Feb – Mar 2020)
- Data visualization specialist course, sponsored by EY. Buenos Aires, Arg. (2018-2020)

### Experience



**Ernst & Young - Senior PMO for Global Operations.** 

Buenos Aires, Argentina (Nov 2018 – Nov 2020)

- Managing tax compliance projects for multinational corporations based in the US, through all its phases (implementation, service delivery, rollover).
- Coordinating deliveries and ensuring timely completion between client and local teams in different countries across the world.
- Responsible of ongoing activities within de project such as, staffing, scope changes, budget, billing, contracting, monitoring and reporting.
- Specialized on large and complex TFO clients (tax finance operations) with 40+ countries (NCR, Diebold, Kontoor). Simultaneously worked with various other projects (Faro, Eden Springs, Tech Data, Precision Valve, Solutions 2Go).
  - Supervisor and career mentor for a team of 6 members.
  - Lead for Training and Innovation committee.
  - Process owner for Implementation and Economics.
  - 4 times awarded with Extra miler for exceptional service.



**Grupo Loyalty – Financial consultant.** 

Buenos Aires, Argentina (Jul 2018 – Nov 2018)

- Advising individuals and companies upon financial issues.
- Planning investment strategies to help customers achieve their financial goals.
- Protecting customer's assets using the proper insurance.



Santander Rio Bank – Ssr. Account executive.

Buenos Aires, Argentina (Dec 2015 – Jan 2017)

- Attending individuals and companies. General administration of accounts, cards, lines of credit, and foreign trade operations.
- Managing security boxes.
- Active commercial participation, making upgrades in my portfolio or generating new clients. Compliance with weekly, monthly and quarterly objectives, both at branch and individual levels.



Castro consultores – Jr. Account executive. Buenos Aires, Argentina (Dec 2014 – Aug 2015)



HDI – Sales administrative assistant. Buenos Aires, Argentina (Feb 2014 – Sep 2014)



Galicia Bank - Senior sales telemarketer. Buenos Aires, Argentina (May 2011 – Sep 2013)